The others didn't need to come?
They're not fond of formal meals.
Kyle?
This feeling...
What?
Kyle, what is the—
Demon!
Demons...
The species controlling the rest of Leunders
and the bane of humanity.
They number far fewer than humanoids,
but individually, they are far stronger.
Currently, not a single nation knows
exactly what the demons are up to.
Three centuries without an attack has been
plenty of time to let our guard down.
Hardly anyone now has ever
seen a demon in the flesh.
But I'm more than familiar.
That horn on her head and that
unique intimidating presence...
She's humankind's greatest foe.
A demon!
Looks like that worked.
Care to taste a few more?
I don't have my armor.
I left Sildonia behind too.
I can't use much magic either.
I've been careless.
I never would've screwed up
like this during the Great Invasion.
Hey! What happened?!
What's going on?
What's this about?!
It's Lord Alzard!
Wait!
She actually ran?
Hey! Summon the other soldiers!
Alzard...
After that, more than half the soldiers
and officials at the empire's embassy
were found brutally murdered.
Strangely, none of the survivors witnessed
anything or even heard a sound.
I've made months' worth
of progress today alone.
Your knowledge is incredible, Sildonia.
You're not bad yourself.
It's impressive you've learned
so much at your age.
How old are you, exactly?
Well, you see...
Tea's ready. Why don't you take a break?
Yeah, okay.
Sorry you had to clean up the place.
Oh, it's fine. I'm used to looking
after Kyle and Theron.
Thanks a ton.
By the way, where is Kyle?
At lunch with a man from the empire.
We're not much for formal meetings.
Aw, man. What a disappointment.
Sorry. My father's been out since this morning.
It is what it is.
Wait, I know. Have you heard anything?
He was acting like he knew something
about a sword comparable to Kyle's.
Maybe he meant the Holy Sword Rand.
The Holy Sword Rand?
Yes.
It was forged in Karan two millennia ago
by a dwarf heralded as an extraordinary smith.
They say Randolph the hero used it
to defeat the demon king of his day.
The sword was dubbed
"Holy Sword Rand" after him.
It's supposedly in the city right now.
My father says he saw it once.
That sounds kind of awesome!
If it really is in Karan, then it's probably
in the possession of Governor Bax.
I see.
Thanks for the tip.
That sounds perfect for me.
Except it's a state treasure,
so I doubt they'd let just anyone have it.
Uh, are you listening?
Goh, does anyone have it out for you?
As you know, I had that dispute
with those debt collectors.
The house is surrounded.
I'd say just under ten men.
And this bloodlust...
They're stronger than
the ruffians from yesterday.
Are they here for us?
Well, we'll know once we capture 'em.
I'll handle most of them.
But some might still make it inside.
Be on your guard.
I-Is this for real?
You can bet on what he says.
He's got a real nose for this sort of thing.
And only this sort of thing.
Goh, you hide in the back.
S-Surely there's something I can do to help.
An amateur won't be of much use here.
You should hide with me.
O-Okay.
You're so calm, Sildonia...
Ask Kyle to pay for a new door.
Oh, you're perfect.
Caught someone to torture
until he spills the beans!
Man, I feel like this is all I do lately.
You guys should run if you don't wanna die.
If you're lucky, you might get away.
That's berrada poison.
A single scratch will immobilize you.
Got it.
Remain calm during battle.
All right.
Oh no! I went overboard!
I was hoping to question him.
Well, Urza will figure something out.
An undine's body is made of water.
Neither daggers nor poisons
are effective against them.
I may have gone a little too far.
Thank you, undine. I appreciate the help.
Poor guy.
Hey, you didn't go much easier than I did.
He'd better be alive.
I mean... I think so?
Thank goodness.
They're alive.
That is good news.
You're both pretty strong.
Why are you standing so far away?
Oh, no reason.
All finished in here too?
Now then...
Why don't you tell us who you are?
Why did you attack us?
I'd recommend you talk, for your own sake.
These ladies behind me
are professional torturers.
The redhead can turn any common
household item into a torture device.
Knives.
Forks.
Even ladles.
She'll slice you up good all over
and rub irritant in each and every wound
so she can enjoy your endless screaming.
But don't go thinking you can
take the easy way out by croaking.
We've got loads of healing potions.
Not to mention...
The elf woman is skilled at keeping
people just short of death.
She'll feed you healing potions just
as your consciousness begins to fade,
all so she can prolong
your suffering, of course.
Eventually, you'd beg me...
to put you out of your misery.
But I'm not a cruel man.
You may be my enemy, but I couldn't
bear to hand you over to them.
We're killing you later.
So if you answer me honestly, I'll let you go.
I'll even pay for your getaway.
But make the call quick.
We have others I'm sure
would be happy to take your place.
W-We were just hired to kidnap that Goh kid.
A kidnapping?
You seemed awful bloodthirsty for that.
We were told we could kill
anyone who got in the way.
Come to think of it, I've been hearing rumors.
They say missing persons
in Karan have been on the rise.
It's not yet known if foul play is involved.
People are going missing?
Is that why Miranda had so many guards?
What happens to the folks getting nabbed?
I don't know.
We were just told to take them
to an empty house outside the city.
Either way, I can't believe
you'd strike in broad daylight.
We were always discreet in the past!
But you're outsiders.
Who'd care if we came straight for you?
He has a point.
The guards still haven't shown up.
All right, so who hired you?
I don't know! Honest!
We've already kidnapped a few people,
but nothing's come of it!
They're probably covering it up!
Which means your employer is fairly powerful.
Yeah. I don't know who it is, but it might be—
Get down!
Huh? What?
Is everyone okay?
Yeah. All good over here.
Let's go after them. Whoever's behind this—
Don't go!
Not this time.
I haven't encountered anyone
this dangerous in a while.
You're not giving chase?
Yeah, no.
I haven't felt anything like that
since seeing my mom at full power.
I suppose I should commend your judgment.
That spell...
was undoubtedly the work of a demon.
The situation is grim.
The damage is extensive, but the
diplomatic issues cannot be ignored either.
You people know what happened, don't you?
Kyle was injured.
Surely you don't think he did it.
He's been cleared of suspicion,
but the real problem is the empire.
They'll insist we're consorting with demons
and issue all manner of rebukes against us.
I know Kyle saw a demon at the embassy,
but are we sure one came after us?
Indeed. That destructive magic
is unique to demons.
They're unsubtle with their spells
because they have so much magic power.
And if they're involved,
then in the worst case...
they could blow the entire city off the map.
It's too dangerous to go
after the demons right now.
First, we should confirm whether Governor Bax
is really involved with the kidnappings.
Miranda, you knew about
the kidnappings, didn't you?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
We were only recently able
to confirm they were happening.
Do you know who's responsible?
No. They're covering their tracks well.
I won't deny it's possible the governor
is involved in the kidnappings.
But I can't make sense of him condoning
such crimes in his own city.
Terrible news! The governor's mansion...
The governor's mansion is on fire!
Someone lend me a hand!
Heave ho!
They beat us to it.
It burned right to the ground. Unnaturally so.
A fire now, of all times?
There's no way that's a coincidence.
I picked through the rubble
but didn't find the Holy Sword Rand.
Don't be a looter.
I came up empty-handed as well.
You can't find the governor?
That's correct.
We haven't even located his body,
even though he was gravely ill and bedridden.
Did demons do this, too?
No, that seems unlikely.
Indeed.
If arson were among their methods,
they would've employed it at the embassy.
Then if demons didn't set this fire...
Our prime suspect is the governor,
who is still unaccounted for.
If he were the mastermind
behind the kidnappings,
it would make sense that he'd start
the fire to destroy evidence.
Either way, we must uncover his whereabouts.
She's so dependable at times like this.
The Miranda I knew was a key figure
in keeping our allies supplied and informed.
But she could be callous.
She wasn't as genial as she is now.
What an awful situation.
Goh! What are you doing here?
We told you to wait with the guards.
Sorry. I heard there was
a fire and got worried.
You're worried about the governor?
No. My father was summoned
by one of his messengers.
What? What are you saying?
I think he might've come here.
Why would the governor summon Gazus?
I don't know.
Does this have anything to do
with Gazus being a candidate for governor?
If so, maybe Bax is behind
the kidnappings after all.
M-Miranda?
Th-This is all my fault...
I'm the one who nominated him
to be the next governor.
What should I do?
I dragged someone so important into this!
If anything happens to him, I...
M-Miranda, we don't know
it's come to that yet.
What's going on? Why is Miranda so distraught?
You think I'm cold, don't you?
N-No, I don't.
I wasn't...
I wasn't always like this, y'know?
I had a lover once.
I see...
But he died because of me.
After that, I gave up on love.
I decided to become heartless and calculating.
The lover she mentioned back then...
Was it Gazus?!
You didn't know they were romantically involved?
Yeah, we had no idea.
My dad's hard to get along with at first,
but he's nice once you get to know him.
Things have been awkward lately, though.
I think my father was avoiding her.
I see.
So Miranda would do things like
come over to feed me sometimes.
Like she was trying to score points.
Score points?
I mean, with Miranda's personality,
she probably thinks this is her last chance.
Better not say that to her face.
If her lover in my previous life was Gazus,
this must be the incident where he died.
I have to think back.
Was there anything else of note?
Hey, you'll catch cold.
This is why I can't stand drunks.
If only...
If only I'd found that
underground passage sooner...
What's up, Kyle? You donned your armor.
I'm going to the governor's mansion.
What? Again?
Yeah. I just realized something.
Urza, I'd like to borrow your magic.
Come with me.
Very well.
Then I'll tag along too.
I haven't given up on the Holy Sword Rand yet.
I-I want in too!
Sure thing.
Goh, look after Miranda until we get back.
Don't leave the embassy.
Okay.
If what Miranda said was for real...
then all the answers lie through
that hidden underground passage.
Next Time
Hidden Ambitions
Next time: "Hidden Ambitions."